Getting irritated at my own failings
21:44         Tokyo Metro, Shibuya Station
Exit 13 (outside the veil)
never has been
and never will be
a part of my life.
I will simply
confront the evils that
force this reality upon us,
and I will simply...
Arrogant bastards.
Episode 36
Dull Knife
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Shibuya Incident
You know my technique, right?
Manipulating crows.
That's it.
22:02 Tokyo Metro Between Meiji Shrine Station and Shibuya Station
Weak, right?
That's why I trained myself so
desperately when I was young.
That way, I could fight without my technique.
It wasn't a waste, either.
Being able to overwhelm you
like this proves that to me.
Stop!
I'll pull out of this incident now!
So please, spare me!
Quiet.
Nee-sama is still in the middle of talking.
So I used to convince myself
that a sorcerer's true value
wasn't their technique.
But you know,
I hit my limit.
I couldn't keep improving
my physical abilities
and the ability to enhance them
with cursed energy forever.
I was crushed.
I had lost heart,
so I decided to confront
my own technique once more,
and that's when I came into full
bloom as a grade 1 sorcerer.
Applause.
Now I'll kill you.
Huh?!
I just wanted to kill time
chatting, anyway.
I'm sorry!
I won't do anything bad ever again!
So please! Please spare my life!
Ui Ui, tell me the value of a life.
How would you measure the weight of a life?
Of course!
It's how valuable they
are to you, Nee-sama!
Thank you.
And you?
Huh? I-I, u-uh...
You can't immediately describe the scale you
use to measure the lives you hunt down.
That's why you lost.
Coincidentally, I measure
lives by their potential assets.
Huh?
Only the veil keeping sorcerers
out just lifted, right?
Even though we just broke
three of these with Ino-san?
22:04 Shuto Expressway No. 3 Shibuya Route
In Front of Cerulean Tower
Either they used all three
to lower one veil,
or two were dummies.
Either way, now sorcerers
can act freely in Shibuya.
That just leaves the veil
trapping Gojo-sensei in,
and the veil trapping ordinary people in.
I wanted to ask this geezer all kinds of
questions, but he won't wake up soon.
We should rejoin Ino-san and—
Ino-san!
The veil's lifted.
What now, Granny?
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What do we do now?
It won't hurt to keep
Satoru Gojo out of play.
So go down below and kill sorcerers.
Grandson?
Who the hell do you think
you're ordering around, old hag?
What's the meaning of this?!
I only channeled the body's information!
Channeled?
Oh, so that's why.
Yes. I've always made it a point not
to channel the soul's information
in order to prevent accidents
like this ahead of time.
I don't really get it,
but my body's special.
I guess it just means this guy's
soul couldn't win against my body.
A soul losing to a body?!
No!
That's impossible!
Kill sorcerers, huh?
You're a sorcerer, too, right?
They hit Ijichi-san?
It sounded like he got attacked
while on the phone with Nitta-chan,
so it probably happened
after he left Fushiguro's group.
He might be in trouble by himself right now.
Nobara, go with Akari-san to Ijichi-san.
We can't use our cell phones in here,
so we won't get anywhere
without the assistant supervisors.
I doubt that idiot would ever lose,
but this whole situation
is smelling even fishier.
I'll take care of things here for now.
That old man is slacking off too much.
Hey, booze.
Ignore him.
Now go.
Right!
Once they're outside the veil,
they'll be able to run if the worst happens.
How's Ino-san?
He's not... okay,
but he's not dead.
I'm going to punch them.
Itadori!
I understand how you feel, but hold back!
What's our highest priority right now?
Gojo-sensei.
The veil was lifted.
The people at the top might
have escaped already anyway.
I'll take Ino-san with me and
head outside the veil for a bit.
Take care of Ino-san for me.
I'll go on ahead to the station.
That's right. That's the best course.
Though operating alone in
Shibuya right now isn't...
All right. But...
If I die, you'll kill me, right?
Don't worry!
I have Mechamaru with me!
Though I haven't heard any response
from Mechamaru for a while now...
So long as you understand.
See you later.
Yeah!
Nee-sama.
Looks like the veil has lifted.
The thought of how much I'll get for
making Satoru Gojo owe me a favor
is making me excited.
That was faster than expected.
Nitta-chan, stop.
21:40 Shoto Bunkamura Street (outside the veil)
Oh, it's a woman in a suit!
I'm so happy!
I was getting sick of them all being men.
Nitta-chan, hide.
I'll finish this quickly.
Pretend to hide in Bunkamura,
then keep going and slip through Tokyu.
From the way he's talking,
he probably took out Ijichi-san.
Which means we need to hurry.
Right!
Kugisaki-san, don't push
yourself too hard, either.
Whispering to each other?
You've got me curious now.
Aw, she went and hid.
Close one!
Coming at me unarmed?
You throwing the match?
I met you before, right?
Most who rely on cursed tools
are mid- or long-range fighters.
So keep up the attack!
Who are you again?
Shooting nails is dangerous, you know.
I'll make it even more dangerous!
Ow!
Hey, so she wasn't hiding!
Nitta-chan!
Shoot!
Why, you!
The sword he dropped earlier?!
How is it above me?!
Too bad.
Hairpin!
Nitta-chan!
Man, you really are dangerous.
Oh, did it hit your chin?
Can't stand?
Hey, can you stand?
Hey, come on...
You know,
you've gotten an awful lot
stronger since we last met.
I didn't even recognize you at first.
Though, you know,
being strong isn't enough
to win in this world.
Especially when my technique is involved.
Though, I don't really understand
my own technique all that well.
Now, which of you should I kill first?
Wh-What...
Work, mouth, work!
...are you after?
Buy as much time as possible!
Oh, they said something about
wanting to seal Satoru Gojo.
I was asking you!
Oh, me? Hmm...
What do you think someone
with a great talent and love
for soccer would do if they were
born in a world without soccer?
That's not right.
I can't explain it well.
Though, is the reason all that important?
Who cares?
It's fun, right?
As long as I have fun, what else matters?!
Don't you think so, too?
Stop it!
Make me stop.
Don't let me commit anymore cli—
Ah, I flubbed it.
It's full of phlegm...
Whoa.
You're totally wobbling!
Yeah, yeah.
It was okay, right?
To kill people in suits that aren't black, too?
JUJUTSU KAISEN
He came to Shibuya with Fushiguro, right?
Nanami-san?
Come on now, look around you.
Why are you strutting this way?
Can't you see I'm holding
a woman hostage here?
Huh?
She ran away.
What's the number and
locations of your allies?
I don't know.
Huh? A wall?
It didn't cut him?!
What's the number and
locations of your allies?!
I don't—
Huh? I died?
I would have died without my technique?!
I-I have to run!
What's the number and
locations of your allies?
I told you, I don't—
I won't let you!
Read the room!
On my way here,
I found several of our
assistant supervisors dead.
That was you, wasn't it?
I-I'm sorry.
He's on a different level.
So this is a grade 1 sorcerer!
Let's make our way to Nitta-san.
Well, now. You, huh?
Mei-san, long time no see.
Quite the thing to say after sending
an assassin after me, Geto-kun.
How is he alive?
Did Gojo-kun screw up last year?
Were Gojo-kun and Geto-kun in on
this whole commotion together?
No, definitely not.
Gojo-kun could kill every person
in this country all on his own.
There would be no need and no point in
setting up these tricks or
getting anyone else involved.
I actually held you in higher regard
than Gojo-kun, you know.
Your nihilistic smile was quite charming.
It's a bitter shame that
I'll have to kill you now.
It really is quite a shame.
This Geto-kun is most likely a fake.
Mei-san, I think it's a shame, too...
that I have to go after
my former upperclassman.
Special-Grade Disease Curse
Smallpox Deity
Curse manipulation?!
Did I read this wrong?
The Special-Grade Disease
Curse, Smallpox Deity.
I did use up my stock
of cursed spirits last year,
but they haven't lost their quality.
Just to be safe, I want to
keep the humans on B5F.
I'll be waiting down this line.
If you manage to exorcise that,
I'll take you on.
Domain Expansion?!
This is a little troublesome.
I've been trapped?
In a coffin, I suppose?
Nee-sama!
Three, two...
How many years has it been...
since something threatened my life?
Nee-sama!
22:10 Shibuya Station Premises
There's absolutely no one here!
I thought there was a huge
crowd trapped inside the station?
So Ijichi-san's okay, then?
I did what I could, and he was
originally aiming to be a sorcerer.
Though it looks you all really
haven't heard about Gojo-san yet.
We entered the building right away,
so that was probably why.
The fact that he's still holding out
after being sealed makes it sound real.
You two, please wait here for rescue.
I'll join Zen'in-san,
and we'll head down to B5F.
I'll go, too!
No, you won't.
I'm the minimum level required
for the fights ahead.
You would hinder me, and be in the way.
Please wait here.
Yuji Itadori!
I'll avenge my brothers!
Ijichi-san! I'll help you with work!
It's fine. I'm fine.
Don't be shy!
We're from the digital native generation!
Excel, Power Point, they're nothing!
I mean it. I'm really fine.
Next time, "Red Scale."
Next Episode
Red Scale
What's "merge cells"?
Do it, do it!
Seriously, go away!